<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ITU solar server</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ITU solar server</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>da-DK</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:06:47 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:06:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/landing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a solar-powered website, which means it sometimes goes offline&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This website runs on a solar powered server located on the roof of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://itu.dk/&#34;&gt;IT university of copenhagen&lt;/a&gt;. This server setup and website came to be during a artist residency by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jacobremin.com/&#34;&gt;Jacob Remin&lt;/a&gt;, hosted by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://ccit.itu.dk/&#34;&gt;Center for Climate IT&lt;/a&gt; in 2024-2025.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This infratructure is meant to be a starting point for students and researchers at ITU interested in working with computation within limits. On your left hand side, in the navigation panel, you can navigate this website and you can launch &lt;a href=&#34;solar.itu.dk/pad&#34;&gt;a collaborative editing pad&lt;/a&gt;. Feel free to use this for your work on and off ITU.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have ideas for things to host on the server or would like to add / edit anything, &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:admin@solar.itu.dk&#34;&gt;please do let us know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This website draws a lot of inspiration from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://solar.lowtechmagazine.com/&#34;&gt;solar website of LOW←TECH MAGAZINE&lt;/a&gt; as well as the &lt;a href=&#34;https://pad.data.coop/&#34;&gt;hedge doc pad&lt;/a&gt; hosted by &lt;a href=&#34;https://data.coop/&#34;&gt;data coop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Made with generous help and support from James Maguire, Frauke Tom H Mennes, Luis Alfredo Landa Mariaca, Sebastian Büttrich, Julian Charles Philip Priest, Yucheng Lu, Halfdan Hauch Jensen and Halfdan Mouritzen.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
